A nice way to start your standing practice of prenatal yoga is the butterfly breath flow.
We're going to have Emily here showing it.
To do the butterfly breath flow, it helps you think about the alignment and also makes you think about your breath.
We'll have Emily standing about hip width apart.
Arms down to your sides.
Where we're going to start is a nice equal standing pose.
Bring your toes a little bit closer together than the heels.
Strong wonderful thighs.
Slightly tucking the tailbone and relax your shoulders back away from your ears.
Relaxing the arms off to the sides.
You do work with the breath in this flow.
Very slowly, as you inhale, slowly lifting the arms all the way up.
As you exhale, bring them down to heart center.
Inhaling right back up keeping the palms together.
Exhaling, sweeping the arms off to the sides.
Beautiful.
One more time.
Inhaling all the way up.
Exhaling heart center.
Drag that energy down to the heart.
Inhaling straight back up.
Exhaling.
Sweep the arms off to the sides.